<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on MacAdmin.fi</title>
    <link>https://macadminfi.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on MacAdmin.fi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://macadminfi.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FinMacAdmin 12.12.2017</title>
      <link>https://macadminfi.github.io/post/finmacadmin_2017_part_deux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macadminfi.github.io/post/finmacadmin_2017_part_deux/</guid>
      <description>FinMacAdmin 2017 pt.2 - First time second time in a calendar year!  Second event of the year takes place in downtown Helsinki, with topics ranging from WiFi to Swift. We will also hear about new things happening in Apple ecosystem - and of course, meet colleagues!
Attending: We are sold out.
However, you can follow the registration page at https://www.regonline.com/FI_EMEIA_TP_ENT_171212_2091372 for cancellations.
Venue: The event will be held in the World Trade Center Helsinki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FinMacAdmin 20.1.2017</title>
      <link>https://macadminfi.github.io/post/finmacadmin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 11:44:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macadminfi.github.io/post/finmacadmin/</guid>
      <description>After a short hiatus, FinMacAdmin is back again - bigger and better than ever!  This year, the organizers will bring you our first ever guests from outside Finnish borders as Henry Stamerjohann (Slack:@henry) from Apfelwerk and Viktor Glemme (Slack:@glemme) from JAMF will be presenting at the event.
Henry and Viktor will be joined on stage by the household names, such as Hannes Juutilainen (Slack:@hjuutilainen) and Janne Lehikoinen (Slack:@fatmrcrab).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finnish Mac Admin Community site</title>
      <link>https://macadminfi.github.io/post/totheinternetz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 01:41:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macadminfi.github.io/post/totheinternetz/</guid>
      <description>Hello Suomalaiset people and others too! Welcome to the new and first home of the Finnish Mac Admin community. These webpages will host information about coming events and occasionally a blog post or two. The best thing is that anybody can take part and contribute - our source code is open on GitHub.
Our small community has been growing rapidly during the past year - so at least for us, 2016 was not that bad afterall.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>